by H.
Thank you for watching
ME
I'm doing a sneak peek of this one, which is my favorite one right now.
Ohhhh!
The member who makes the chairman of the judging committee, Mr. Himura, the most excited will be crowned as the queen!
This time, we'll start with what Umeza Ume is into right now. I wonder what Ume is into?
So today I'm going to show you that it's not just about food at the Umeza.
I'll introduce you to the plum shop...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes...
As you all know, I'm a huge fan of fragrances. I've tried room diffusers, room sprays, candles...
I've tried room diffusers, room sprays, candles, etc., but they heal me like nothing else.
I really don't want to tell you about some of the incense that I recommend, but my favorite store is Danlow.
I don't really want to tell you about it, but my favorite shop is Danlow, and their incense is so stylishly packaged that I often try to burn it.
I'm really into this incense, and when I burn it, I think it spreads...
Can I eat this? I don't eat this.
Smell it, it's different from when it's blown.
It's a deep blend of globe cinnamon, rose amber, stimulating, gentle, and sometimes deceptive.
What did you just say?
Globe and what? Globe Cinnamon, First Mint and what?
No, no, no, no. Baseball. That's not baseball.
I'd like to give it to a member at least once, but I don't think girls are supposed to pass it around like it's some fresh scent or something.
I'm sure they'll just pass them around like that. You don't know what I'm talking about.
You want to go to the second row? You're not going to the second row.
You know what I mean?
This...
But when you cook incense, it smells a little burnt afterwards.
Maybe it's not the right incense.
This one has a really nice scent that drifts away.
In addition to that, I would like to recommend you to use this as well.
Suburban ambient sounds.
I'm definitely the kind of person who wants sound when I get home.
I think everyone turns on music or the TV right away.
But when I'm really tired, I get too much information and words, and it makes me tired.
Oh my God, I'm too tired.
When I'm really tired, I hear the sound of bicycles and cars.
That's when you get tired?
That's right.
It's like this.
What, does it calm you down?
It calms me down.
When I go home, I burn incense, play this sound on my phone, and sit down on the sofa and take a breath, I feel really good.
It's like the sounds of everyday life are really calming.
I listen to the sounds of forests and water.
There was a time when I did.
It's like I just passed by there.
I like to listen to this set when I'm awake.
It's very urban, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's pretty urban.
You'd think I'd want to get away from here, but I guess not.
That's why I intentionally play sounds from the forest when I walk along the Yamato Mountain Road.
There was a time when I did that.
But now, over here...
You must be really sick, Mr. Umeda.
Ume was so busy with the stage and live performances
If it weren't for this, I'd probably have gone away.
You've helped me so much.
Wait a minute, it looks like Umeda-san died there!
The next Imasuki presenter is Kurokai.
Next up is Kurokai.
Kurokai, you slipped on the sickle.
That was scary to watch.
I wonder why... that should've been more popular.
That's right.
I don't think it's the Kurokai's fault, but rather the responsibility of the whole group.
Let's think about it again.
We don't want that to be the end of something so important.
It's definitely a waste.
So let's think about it.
Let's have a meeting to think about the sickle cut.
Let's see what Kurokai recommends.
Today I would like to introduce you to...
The best snack food in the world!
My favorite snack!
Everyone has their own favorite snack.
This is the one!
This is the one you can talk about till morning.
This is the one.
Heart Chips.
They've been around forever.
You've never heard of it.
It's a local thing, like the big souls.
It's not nationwide.
You don't know Heart Chips?
No.
You don't know?
I'll bring you some next time.
I don't get it.
Why do you have a heavy futon on the floor with heart chips?
I don't know.It's true.
I don't know what that means.
Heart chips, I'm gonna introduce you guys to some people... next time.
I don't get it.
So here's my best snack.
I don't know.
I've never seen it before.
Yes, you have.
I don't know.
I've never seen it before.
That's right.
It's called a submarine lo hinabeh.
It's called Submarine Lo Hinabe.
It's very stylish.
It's a free gift while you're waiting.
It's a free gift.
Heh.
Hinabe's
Kuromi calls it the best
the snacks you get while you wait.
Let's try it!
Bon appétit!
It's good, but...
But it's so good!
I must have set the bar really high!
LOL!
It's funny, I don't feel anything.
LOL.
It's delicious.
It's delicious, but...
They say it's the best snack.
I thought, "How good can it be?
I can do that.
I'm surprised you said that.
I don't eat a lot of snacks.
They're good, they're really good, but...
Let everyone try the Heart Chipotle.
Heart Chipotle is very strong.
Are you guys eating it?
They're good.
It's delicious.
They're good, but you're setting the bar too high.
They're called the best snack around.
Oh, oh, oh!
LOL!
All five Imasuki presentations have been completed so far!
The member who sticks out the most in the Hyomura
will be crowned Imasuki Queen!
Tar lawsuits
Yamashita's 숨
I didn't know it for 3 seconds. I ate it and it was delicious.
I was hooked on it. Everything else was good too, but the surprise was shocking.
It was the worst first impression I've ever had.
It was the worst.
I wish we could do that.
The other way around.
Well, Don...
And here we go... the bananaman of Nogisaku and Koteide.
I'm Bananaman, Nogisaku Koteide Shika no Bananaman.
Yay!
Yay Yay Yay
WARALE-LE-LE-LE
Walla-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
Se-no
One dreams twice
One more time, one more time
People dream twice
Nice
Yay
People dream twice
Let's do the project we're going to do today, please announce it.
Here we go!
Quiz Double Setter
We're going to quiz Kubo Yamashita, the double-setter of the new song, to make the two center members impregnable once again!
And depending on the number of correct answers, there will be a prize!
If you get all the answers right and make it to the end, they will give you 1,000,000 yen!
That's impossible in today's TV!
It's not like it's going to cost a million dollars.
But the prize money is reduced according to the number of incorrect answers.
If you get 7 questions wrong, the prize money is zero and the quiz is over.
And if you don't know the answer to a question, you can ask a member of the raffle for a hint.
You can ask a member of the lottery for a hint.
You can use this card up to 5 times.
Can I use it five times?
You can use it five times?
This is a million dollars.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
So, if there's a question I know the answer to, why don't you guys just say so?
Let's get that part right.
It cost me a million dollars.Because it cost a million dollars.
If we deem it fraudulent, we'll cancel it immediately.
So it's canceled.
And then you'll all have to leave.
Oh, no.
Let's not do this to Okuda.
Suddenly... the support group will be back-loaned.
There'll be nothing left.
Just a back-loan support group.
It'd be a broadcast accident.
I'll show something.
I'll show a still image of you guys, or something.
I'll show a still image of you guys or something.
This is what we're doing.
Let's do it right.
Kumamoto Yamashita is really...
You can't say that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's right.
After I answer.
What's that?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Like, "Good luck," of course.
That's okay.
We'll both keep our most zero expressions on our faces for the rest of the day.
Yeah, that's good.
Oh, thank God.
This may be a boring broadcast, but...
Oh, man... oh, man... oh, man...
The sooner this is over, the sooner we can get to Yamashita and Kubo.
That's right.
Azadora and Taiga.
We didn't give these two great actresses enough time.
It's true.
The faces in the staff introductions...
You're right.
You've got to love these two, they're so good.
People thought it was a show that couldn't cook.
I wish you the best of luck.
I'm aiming for a million yen.
Let's go for it!
Let's go!
Answer correctly and keep the million yen.
The first respondent is Kaki.
If I make a mistake here...
Yes, sir.
You'll suddenly be out 500,000 yen.
That's a lot of pressure.
Yes, it is.
50 from 100 is a lot of pressure.
But you've been with us for a long time.
I've been a fan for a long time.
It's all right.
Then...
Double center.
First question.
Deden.
Deden there, you say, Mr. Shimono.
Read out the whole question.
Parents don't have Deden either.
The first question is
Yamashita took for his first appearance on the show after joining the company.
questionnaire that he took for his first appearance on the show after joining the group.
Mizuki Yamashita
Yes, I am.
Questionnaire for his first appearance on the show after joining
Running as a hobby
What do you like to watch?
Did you write
Four choices.
I did it!
I turned very gently.
Four choices.
Panda.
Two.
goat
flamingo
Otter
Come on. Come on.
You already know the answer.
This is already easy.
Uh, yeah.
Let's go then.
A million yen.
If I make a mistake, it's another 500,000 yen.If I'm wrong, it's another 500,000 yen.
It's costing you a million, Kaki.
I'm really confident about this.
I saw this so I went to that café and took a picture of it
Eh?
Cafe
Fantastic.
Okay, Kaki, here's your answer.
The answer is 3, flamingo.
Please tell me if I'm right or wrong, Mr. Himura.
Correct!
Brilliant! I remembered it already!
You're so smart.
So... there's something going on here.
Yes! There was some magazine feature on flamingos.
I'm going to be a flamingo.
Yes! He painted flamingos.
You painted flamingos.
I bought that too.
He said he liked those flamingos, so I wanted to be a flamingo too.
We went to a flamingo café and the whole family
And we took a picture of the flamingo and took a notice together.
Wow!
That makes me happy.
I'm so happy.
You remember Yamashita?
Yamashita, did you remember this?
Yes, I did! But I wanted to be a flamingo.
When I was little.
You really wanted to be a flamingo?
My dream was to be a flamingo.
I guess that dream died out.
It didn't come true.
My dream didn't come true, but I remembered it.
No! Brilliant!
Congratulations on your one million game!
It's the end of the quiz to continue with the one million yen project.
You made a nice flow of the quiz earlier.
By the way, did you get the first question, Flamingo?
Oh, I got it too.
Yes!
There's a good chance I'm going to win a million yen.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll get it!
See you!
It's like we're having a break here.
Next is a project right after the third term students appeared on the show for the first time.
This is from a question Kubo wrote in the questionnaire for the "Only in my house" grand prix.
A question from one of Kubo's sentences
Kubo wrote a statement of determination at the end of the 2017 This is My Family Only Grand Prix survey.
At the end of the questionnaire for the 2017 This is My Family Only Grand Prix, Mr. Kubo wrote a statement of determination.
I have decided to do my best in the recording.
I will work harder!
Now for the "Onyarara" part.
What on earth did you decide?
Four choices.
Really?
Four choices is so sweet.
I don't care if you had to choose 100 options.
1. not to be an ornament
2. don't cry
3. leave a mark
4. make Mr. Bananaman smile
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, go for it!
Come on, Kubo. It's 2017. That means it's been about six years.
Right... you got in...
You've made up your mind. If you get it wrong, it's half a million yen.
Good luck. Get out of here.
All right, you've made your decision.
All right, let's go.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
It's okay. It's okay.
You decide what the answer is, go ahead.
Number two, no crying.
No. 2, no crying.
How about it, Mr. Himura?
Please
Which one?
Correct!
Yay!
So this one was a little more mountainous.
It's a little more mountainous. I mean, I'm lost between the two.
But I got the impression that she was crying during the recording.
That's why I decided on this one.
I see...
The reason I was torn between the two was to leave a mark.
I see.
This last part... it's out of the frame.This last part is already outside the box.
I'm writing outside the box on the survey.
I've decided not to cry at recordings anymore.
I'll do my best.
I'm looking forward to working with you in the future.
I'll be counting on you.
You're so serious.
She really cried too much.
She's a real pain in the ass.
Well, I can't help it.
When she came in, everyone was crying.
Even Himemaru was crying.
I was crying.
Hime-Maru-san was bawling, bawling, bawling, bawling.
You were crying, too.
Well done!
All right, we're still in the million-yen kitchen.
Yay!
A million here!
That's a perfect score!
Here we go! 1,000,000 yen in prize money!
Now we have 1,000,000 yen in prize money, and Yoda is the one who keeps trying.
Don't worry.
It's definitely Yoda.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Yoda and I have known each other for a long time.
Yeah, we're in the same boat.
I remember everything... everything.
You don't strike me as the remembering type.
If I'm told correctly...
Now the third question.
Third question.
Yodaeno.
Good luck.
Question 3.
There it is.
I wonder if I'll last.
The next problem also talks about a unique family rule
This one was written by Yamashita, the only one in our family to win the Grand Prix.
Question from an unpublished questionnaire
Mizuki Yamashita is a member of
This is just for our family Grand Prix questionnaire.
In the "Rules for our family only" section
What do you shout when you come home?
Four choices.
I'm home board
I'm home Trix
I'm home Iker Jackson
I'm home
TADAIIMA WHAT'S THAT?
I'm begging you.
Yamashita Mizuki's house. Our house rules.
May I ask you to say something?
How about this?
What do you think?
As long as you don't say anything weird.
As long as you promise me that.
Okay.
Can you promise me that?
I'll be fine.
Don't stress. Just the right answer.
Then let's have Yamashita himself tell us everything.
One, please.
I'm home, Abbodorov.
Yes, two.
I'm home, Trix.
Next.
I'm home. Iker Jackson.
Yes, sir.
I'm home, Moss.
I mean, I was surprised at how low everything was.
I mean, I'm surprised at how low everything is.
This is Asadora
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is real tension.
This is the real tension.
Yes, sir.
Surprisingly, all of us.
I think I understand.
Now...
Oh, my God.
They look exactly the same.
If you get it wrong, it's half of the 500,000 yen.
That's good.
Then, please answer the question.Now, please answer the following questions.
Number 1, TADAIMA ABO DOUGHU
I'm home, AboDofu.
Mimura, correct or incorrect?
Shame! Shame!
Shame!
What a pity!
Such a shame!
I'm home, not tofu.
I'm down to 50 pieces.
I'm sorry.
Half.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Mammoth, right?
Yes, we had two choices.
Mammoth. You're right.
I'm so sorry.
Why did I think it was Bean Curd?
Because...
It looked so good.
I see.
Too bad.
It can't be helped.
But someone will make a mistake. Someday.
And then your back will disappear in a cloud of sugar.
Where does love go when it's swept away by the waves of memory?
In Harajuku, where we met that day
I never thought I'd say goodbye
I always waved to you from this pedestrian bridge
I wonder if you can forget me so much that you never look back
Now, that wave will never return
Thank you for watching
I've never looked back
How can you forget me?
Now the sea will never return
shimmering beautifully in the wind
You have no regrets
My heart is so clear
I've been looking for you for so long that I can no longer see you
Ripples of Love
Tickets to watch the streaming of Under Live are now on sale!
Next Quiz: The Second Half of the Double Center
Digging deeper into the unknown aspects of the two
What will you do with it?
I'm nervous.
Yes, I am
Oh, that's a funny face.
Yeah, I want to pull it back.
Please subscribe to our channel.